<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Da Gabe Agenda</title>
    <link>blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Da Gabe Agenda</description>
    <generator>Hugo 0.125.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 18:35:57 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>blog/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 18:35:57 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>blog/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me&#xA;My name is Gabe - I&amp;rsquo;m a game designer &amp;amp; music maker based in Ontario, Canada.&#xA;When I&amp;rsquo;m not clocked in working on a AAA game, I&amp;rsquo;m thinking about art, science and philosophy, or working on side projects for fun.&#xA;I decided to start this blog thing to have a convenient place to put blurbs on topics I&amp;rsquo;m interested about. Anything from lists of cool drug trip scenes in games, or essays about whatever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beer Pong? More Like Beer Wrong</title>
      <link>blog/posts/blog/bad-design-beer-pong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>blog/posts/blog/bad-design-beer-pong/</guid>
      <description>I am currently stuck in the U.S.A, in a hotel in Irving, Texas waiting for my 4am flight to Charlotte, North Carolina, which will only then take me to Toronto, Ontario (that one&amp;rsquo;s in Canada) and since I now find myself with hours to spend stewing in a small room with some mini-fridge whiskey and and a Quarter-Pounder with Cheese meal paid for by American Airlines, I started thinking about a conversation I had with one of my best friends a while ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burnout, Jobs, and Adulthood</title>
      <link>blog/posts/blog/burnout-jobs-and-adulthood/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>blog/posts/blog/burnout-jobs-and-adulthood/</guid>
      <description>For the past two years I&amp;rsquo;ve been working as a game designer on a AAA studio, and it&amp;rsquo;s been fantastic so far! I never really imagined working at this scale; in fact at some point - when I was in college - I said &amp;ldquo;I will never work in a huge AAA studio&amp;rdquo;. Hahaha I hope they don&amp;rsquo;t read this.&#xA;In 2021 my work permit in Canada was expiring, which meant if I hadn&amp;rsquo;t found employment in my field I would&amp;rsquo;ve been promptly kicked out of here and back to Brasil.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing The Blog</title>
      <link>blog/posts/blog/introducing-the-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>blog/posts/blog/introducing-the-blog/</guid>
      <description>One of the things I do a lot is get high and go off on a rant about an incredibly niche topic I find fascinating. I&amp;rsquo;m also incredibly lucky to have friends that not only put up with that, but at times even find that amusing.&#xA;Not every rant is merited, but every now and then something of note comes out of my head. Unfortunately, that is usually forgotten the next day unless someone wrote it down and reminded me of it later.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
